Guide to the Jerald Brauer Papers 1925-1999
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Correspondence, 1940-1970
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1958-1965
    - H, Hadsell Hakes, J. Edward Hamre, James S. Hance, Kenneth Handy, Robert T. Hansen, Herbert Hanson, Paul A. Harbers, Elizabeth Harmon, Francis Harmon, R.K. Harms, John W. Harrelson, Walter Harris, Charles Harris, Rogers Hartig, Theodore Hatlestad, Selmer Hawley, Deborah Hefner, Phil Herhold, Robert Hesla, David H. Heydenriech, Elaine Hill, George W. Hiltner, Seward Hilton, O.A. Hodges, Eva Hoffman, Cecil Holloway, John Hollis, Michael Holman, Charles T. Holtzmann, David Marshall Hopkins, Jeannette Howe, Reuel Hudson, Winthrop Huggins, Lu Hunt, John W. Hunter, Lemuel Hutcheson, R.G. Hutchison, John A. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - I-K, Ikenberry, Oliver S. Ingle, Dwight Jackson, Herbert Jacobsen, George Jamison, Leland Janney, J. Elliot Jellema, William Johnson, D. Gale Johnson, Howard A. Johnson, Ralph M. Josselyn, Franklyn Keith, William A. Kemper, Margaret Kimpton, Lawrence Kennedy, Gerald Kern, Martin Kerney, LeRoy G. Keyes, Fenton Kimpton, Lawrence A. Knopf, Edwin Knowles, Richard Koch, C. Franklin Koenker, Ernest Kolb, William L. Kraeling, Carl H. Kraft, Charles F. Krauss, Paul H. Kribben, Earl Kring, Walter D. Krodel, Gottfried Kucharsky, David (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - L, Lawson, E. THomas Leaden, J. Warren Leavenworth, Lynn Ledbetter, J.T. Leen, Walter Leibrecht, Walter Lessly, Stiles Lester, Julius Liberman, Grace L. Lind, Millard Lish, Gordon Loder, Dwight Loew, Cornelius Lokken, Sigurd Long, Charles Loomis, George W. Louzecky, David J. Luman, Richard Lunding, Franklin Lacy, Graham G. Landt, Dan Lazareth, William H. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - M, McAllaster, Allan McCanna, Henry McCaw, John E. McCord, James I. McCormack, Clyde McCormick Theological Seminary McCutcheon, W.J. McMath, Neil C. MacLennan, David Madsen, David Maitland, David J. Marks, Rachel B. Matsuoka, S. Mattson, Karl Maye, Arthur Meacham, Paul L. Mead, Sidney Meitzen, Manfred Michaelsen, Robert Miller, Alexander Miller, Dale Miller, Samuel Miller, William Minto, Rabb Moehring, Horst Moeller, Elmer Monk, Robert Moore, Joseph R. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Mor-Mu, Morgan, Russell Morlion, Felix Morris, W.S. Morrison, H.T. Mortimer, C.G. Mowry, Lucetta Mortimer, Charles J. Murakami, Masayoshi Murphy, Steve Muth, Philip Arthur (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - O-N, Nakamura, Hajime Nelson, E. Clifford Nelson, Roland Neilsen, Ernest Norddeutscher, Lloyd Bremen Normann, Raymond M. Nyholm, Paul C. Obenhaus, Victor Oberholzer, Emil Ogden, Schubert Olson, Perry T. Oppegard, Margaret Osborn, Robert Outler, Albert Overgaard, Herman Palda, Kristian Pannebaker, Gregory Parr, Clarence E. Parvis, Merrill Patchen, Clinton J. Pattullo, Andrew Pavy, Roy Gilmour Penelhum, Terence Pennebraker, Gregory Penny, Freeland Perry, Joseph Sam Pickle, Joseph Pike, James A. Plaisance, Barbara Ann Plampin, Geoffrey Price, Walter Van Prohaska, John Pyle, John W. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - R-Z, Rosenberg, Charles Samuel, V.C. Sandeen, Ernie Schultz, T.W. Schwantes, Charles Scoon, Robert Seyda, Arthur Sharpe, D.R. Shelburne Hotel Snyder, Ross Stendahl, Krister Stump, John P. Taylor, Charles L. Tobias, Robert Ullery, David Wagoner, Walter Watkins, George Wentz, Frederick Whetstone, Harold White, Helen F. Wickey, Gould Willoughby, Harold Winter, Gibson Withers, Lucille World Council of Christian Education Worship Committee (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3: Correspondence, 1960-1963
    - A-C, Abingdon Press African Methodist Episcopal Church Antaios AATS Arizona, University of Bethel Church, Milwaukee, Wisconsin Board of World Mission Bowdoin College Bowman, Carroll California, University of Calvary Baptist Church Chapin-May Foundation Christ Church Cranbrook Cornell College Christianity and Crisis Christianity Today Colorado State University Concordia College Concordia Theological Seminary Congregation Rodfei Zedek Convention of the South Cornell College Chicago Rabbinical Council Crozer Theological Seminary Crusade of Mercy Campaign Curtis, Fred A. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Organizations, 1960-1963, D-K, Dell Publishing Company Directory of American Scholars Dover Publishing Educational Testing Service Elgin State Hospital Elizabethtown Hospital Encyclopedia Americana Fuller Theological Seminary Gary, First Baptist Church of Gettysburg Colleges Health, Education and Welfare, Department of Heidelberg College Huron College Illinois State Fair Housing Bill Illinois Baptist State Convention Immaculate Conception Seminary Institute for Religion and Social Studies Institute on Scriptural Theology Kansas Baptist Convention (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Organizations, 1960-1963, L-N, Life Magazine Lutheran Theological Seminary Lutheran Quarterly Lutheran World McMaster University Methodist Publishing House Methodist Church, Board of Education Minneapolis Council of Churches Muhlenberg College National Association of Biblical Instructors National Council of Teachers of English Nelson, Thomas and Sons Newcomers Orientation Program Newsweek Northern Baptist Theological Seminary Northwestern Lutheran Theological Seminary Northwestern University (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Organizations, 1960-1963, O-W, Oberlin College Off the Cuff Pacific School of Religion Pageant Palmer House Pennsylvania State University Presbyterian Institute of Industrial Relations Princeton Inn Princeton Theological Seminary Random House, Inc. Regent's Park College Religion in Life Ripson College Scribner's, Charles Sinai Congregation Southern Methodist University Texas Lutheran College Shellburne Hotel Swedenborg Philosophical Centre Southern Baptist Theological Seminary Southern Methodist University Time Magazine United Presbyterian Church United States District Court Valparaiso University Virginia Union University Washington University Saint Louis Western Theological Seminary Winston, John C., Company Wittenberg University (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 4: Correspondence, 1961-1965
    - Aa-Arm, Aaron, Ely Abbott, C. F. Abatso, George Abbott, Cleon Abbott, Walter Abe, Masao Abrecht, Paul Abromowitz, M. Adams, Charles Adams, James Luther Adams, John Maxwell Adams, Phillip Adelman, Ethel Aden, LeRoy Alstrom, Gosta Ahner, Eugene Ahern, Barnabas Ahlers, Rolf Ahlstrom, G. W. Ahlstrom, Sidney Akers, Milburn Akiyama, T. Albaugh, Gaylord Albert, Harold Albus, Harry Alexander, Rolf Alexandre, Clement Alexis, Gerhard Alfrink, Bernard Allen, Paul Allen, Yorke Allewaert, Rene Allin, J. Bryan Allison, L. M. Altizer, Thomas Ambrose, W. Hayden Amelung, Eberhard American Airlines American Baptist Convention American Consul General, Germany Ammon, George Andersen, Earven Anderson, Bernhard Anderson, Edwin Anderson, George Anderson, Hurst Anderson, Leila Anderson, Stuart St. Angelo, George Appel, Andre Appleby, David Aquinas, M. Arbaugh, George Arendt, Hannah Armstrong, Tom Armed, Hugh (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Arn-Ayer, Arnold, Ernest Arnold, Harvey Arnold, W. Joseph Arnold, Mel Arnold, Tracy Arnott, Robert J. Ashanin, C. B. Ashley, Benedict M. Ashley, Robert P. Atlantic Hotel Atwater, Eastwood Auchincloss, Douglass Audrey, Mary Auer, Nancy Austin, James Ambrose, Haydn Austin, James Averill, Lloyd Ayer, Hugh (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Ba, Back Copy Department Bachmann, C. Charles Barlett, Donald B. D. Committee Bachmann, E. Theodore Bachmeyer, Tim Bader, Claudia Bage, M. Bagnell, Kenneth Bagration, Irene Bahr, Gordon Bailey, J. Martin Bailey's Hotel Bainton, Roland Baiz, John Baken, David Baker, David Baker, Oren Bailer, Stuart Ban, Joseph Banes, Carl Bangs, Carl Barbour, Ian Bardy, Robert Barkwell, Gordon Barnes, Roswell Barth, Karl Barta, Robert Barth, Markus Bartlett, Donald Bartlett, J. F. Bartlett, Josiah Batchelder, Robert Bates, Robert Battanhouse, Roy Bautz, Donald Batson, Robert Bauer, Arthur Baum, Gregory Baumgartner, Paul (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Be-Bl, Bea, Augustin Beach, Peter Beadle, George Beadles, Owen Beane, Wendell Beare, Frank Beattie, Paul Beaver, R. Pierce Beck, Alfred Beck, Kenneth Becker, Arthur Becker, C. H. Becker, Russell Beckman, Peter Bedikian, A.A. Beittel, Adam Beliard, Jean Bell, Cyril Bell, Robert K. Belter, E.W. Bender, Gerald Bender, Ross Benedict, Wilbur Benes, Louis Benne, Robert Benner, Herman Bennett, Edward Bennett, John Benson, Dennis Benson, J. Victor Benton, William Benz, Ernst Bergendoff, Conrad Berggren, Paul Bernards, Solomon Bernier, Jeanne-Marie Berthold, Fred Bertram, Mark Bertram, Walter Bertram, Robert Beth, Elmer Bethke, Clayton Beto, George Bettison, Morse Binder, Leonard Binder, Frederick Bjorling, Fred Blake, Eugene Blakemore, W. B. Blackwell, B. H. Blakemore, Barnett Blethen, Margaret Bloesch, Donald Blewett, John Blumengarten, Louis (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Bo-Browin, Board of Elections, Chicago Board of Theological Education Bock, Paul Bock, Walter Bohmfalk, Erwin Bonaventure, Archabbot Bonker, Milus Bordeaux, University of Booty, John E. Borden, Stanley Borg, Daniel Borneman, Robert Bornkamm, Heinrich Bosley, Harold Bowerman, Emma Braaten, Carl Bradley, W. E. Braga, George Braisted, Paul Brasted, Evelyn Bosshart, Robert Bouscaren, H. G. Bouwman, Gracie Bowman, Clarice Boyack, James Boyd, T. Boyer, Richard Bowersox, Glen Brauer, Jerald Bremer, David Brenneman, Walter Brethren Press Brewer, Earl Brewster, George Brewster, William Bridges, Kenneth Bridston, Keith Bring, Ragnar Brinkley, Cosby Brinkmann, Ernst Brosseder, Johannes Browin, Frances (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Brown-Byers, Brown, Aubrey Brown, D. Mackenzie Brown, Dale Brown, David Brown, D. Mackenzie Brown, Evelyn Brown, Harrison Brown, Luella Brown, Nancy Brown, Ray Brown, Robert Brown, Robert McAfee Browne, Eleanor Browning, Don Bruere, Richard Brunn, Irving Bruins, Elton Brune, Audrey Bruninga, C.L. Bruno, Hal Bryan, Monk Bucks, Emory Stevens Buckley, George M. Buckstaff, John Buhl, Albert Bulkey, Robert Bultmann, D. R. Burbank, Roland Burdick, Oscar Burke, Bernard Burke, Dorothy Burke, Margaret Burke, Patrick Burkhart, John Burleigh, John Burmeister, Henry Burness, Carl Burnite, David Burton, Kenneth Bursar's Office Buschmann, Walter Buseman, Fred Butler, J. Donald Butler, John M. Buttrick, David Butts, T. L. Butz, Otto Byers, Ralph (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Cad-Chitt, Cadigan, Robert J. Cahill, Arthur R. Cahill, Joseph Calkins, Raymond Callahan, John L. Canadian Imperial Bank of Commerce Cannon, William Dean Carberg, Warren Career Counseling and Placement Carillo, Juanarius Carlson, Arnold E. Carlson, Earland Carnell, Edward John Carpe, William Donald Carr, Aute Cartland, D.L. Case, Leland D. Cavanaugh, Thomas Centennial Celebration, Special Committee on Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions Chadwick, Henry Chandler, Edgar Chandler, John W. Chandran, Joshua Chaney, Charles Chase, Francis S. Chave, Ernest Chicago Theological Seminary Chittenden, Hugh B. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Christian-Coh, Christian Register Christian, William A. Christianson, Clifford Church History Field Meeting Cirker, Hayward Clark, Samuel I. Clements, J. H. Clive, John Coambs, Eleanor Cobb, William Daniel Coburn, John B. Coffman, Stewart Coggeshall, Lowell Cohen, Sigmund Cohen, Arthur (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Col-Conze, Coles, J. Preston Collins, Gordon Colmex, Omar Martinex Colston, Lowell Colwell, Ernest Comptroller, Office of the Cone, Fairfax Congar, Yves Congar, Robert Conley, Keiran Connery, John R. Constantine, Leo Conway, Martin Conze, Edward Cooke, Bernard Cooper, Claude Cooper, John C. Conze, E. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Cor-Cut, Corbett, George Corey, Kendall Cornell, William A. Cornelsen, Rufus Cortelyou, W.T. Corzine, William Cotton, Albert Cour, Raymond Le Couteur, E.R. Cowan, Wayne Cox, James C. Crabb, R. Weldon Cragg, Gerald Craig, W.D. Crary, Calvert Crawford, Lee Allen Cremer, Marlies Cressman, Lloyd Crockett, William Crosby, Arthur Crossan, Dominic Crowley, Patrick Crummey, D. Clifford Cull, David J Cully, Kendig Brubaker Cummings, Walter Cuneo, John F. Cunningham, Sarah Cuninggim, Merrimon Curtis, Charles Cushman, Robert Cutshall, E. Guy (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Da-Dickson, Dahood, Mitchell Dahl, Erno Daley, Richard J. Dana, Ellis H. Daniel, Irene Daskam, Max Daugherty, D.H. Davidson, Arthur Davidson, Glen Dean, Eric Dean, Thomas Dean, William Debbins, William DeBoer, Lawrence Decter, Moshe Dederer, Henry Deeter, Emily Dehmel, Fritz Dehollain, Christien Deisher, Mary Sue De Kay, Drake Denham, Robert DeMenil, Jean DeVries, Jan DeWitt, Robert L. Dickson, Ronald (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Diers-Dou, Diers, Herman Dillenberger, John Dilley, Frank Directory of American Scholars Dirks, J. Edward Dirks, Lee E. District Director of Internal Revenue, Internal Revenue Service Divinity School Extension Work D.Mn. Committee Dokmo, Rolf Doll, Henry Dorschel, Querin Dores, Edmund Dotson, Earl Douglas, William (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dowd-Dyme, Dowey, Edward Downes, Stanley Drake, George Drew, George Droege, Thomas Dronberger, Ilse Duba, John Dubocq, John W. Duchesne-Guillemin, Jacques Duling, G. Harold Dumezil, G. Duncan, Robert C. Dunn, Ruth Durgin, Lawrence Dyck, Cornelius Dyer, E. John (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - E, Eagle, Vernon Earhart, Byron Earnest, A.T. Eastern Clergy Bureau Eckardt, A. Roy Edwards, O.C. Egan, Gerald Egan, John J. Ehnmark, Erland Eickhoff, Andrew Eisenberg, Irving Eisenbeis, Walter Elhard, Leland Eliade, Mircea Eldridge, Roger Elifson, Donald Eller, Paul Elliott, Frank Elliott, Patrick Elliott, William Ellis, John Tracy Ellison, Ralph Ellis, William S. Ellul, Jacques Ellwood, Scott Elmer, Franklin Emple, Paul Enan, Beryl Endress, Henry England, J. Martin English, Darrell D. English, Maurice Enquist, Roy J. Epp, Fred Erickson, R.F. Erling, Bernhard Esler, David Esper, Erwin Espy, R. H. Edwin Eusden, John Evangelical Lutheran Theological Seminary Evans, Emory Evans, Joseph P. Eversole, Finley Exeter, Bishop of Exman, Eugene (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Fa-Fog, Fackre, Gabriel Faculty, Divinity School Fahs, Charles B. Fair, The Fair, Harold Fairweather, Eugene Fargo, Jerry Farley, Hugh D. Farris, Allan Fate, Russell Fehl, Noah Feilding, Charles Feingold, Jessica Feldstein, Charles Felix, Richard Feller, Lorence Fellowships and Scholarships, Committee on Fendt, E.C. Fennell, William Fenner, Betty Ferm, Robert L. Ferm, Vergilius Fey, Harold Fitchter, Joseph Fichter, Robert Field Chairman Filas, Francis Filbey, Emery Fildey, Harold Finch, William Finn, James Fischer, Robert Fitch, Donald Fitch, Robert Fitzpatrick, Mallary Fixler, Michael Fletcher, Verne Florovsky, Georges Flory, Charles Flottorp, Haakon Fogde, Myron (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fol-Fus, Foley, Malachy Foote, Willard Forman, Charles Forrest, Alexander Foster, Arthur Foster, H.L. Fraenkel, Peter Frank, Janice Franken, Darrell Frasure, Carl Frei, Hans Frejborn, Lennart Friedrich, L.W. Fritz, Charles E. Froehlig, James Frost, Stanley Fry, August Fry, Franklin Fryden, Floyd Fulton, Everett Funk, Paul Funkay, William Fussler, Herman (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Gaf-Gra, Gaffey, James Gale, Horace Gallagher Gambke Gamble, Connolly Gamma Photo Lab Gandy, Samuel Gannon, John Mark Gapp, Kenneth Garber, Sheldon Garrish, Bryan Garrison, W.E. Garrison, Winfred Gart, Murray Gartner, Bertil Gaus, John E. Geanakoplos, Deno Genz, Leonard Geoghegan, William Gerberding, R.H. Gerrish, Brian Gerstenmaier, Eugen Gevik, J. Dean Gezork, Herbert Gibbs, Mark Gibson, Boyd Gibson, Charles Gibson, Samuel Giddens, Paul Gieseman, A. Wayne Gilbert, Glenn Henkricks, William L. Gilkey, Langdon Gill, Theodore Gillette, Gene Gilpatric, Chadbourne Gladfelter, Millard Glatzer, N.N. Glick, G. Wayne Godby, John Goheen, Robert Gold, Victor Golden, Sam Goldsmith, Dale Goddard, James Goldstein, Robert Good, Edwin Good, Harry Goodennough, Erwin Goodman, Howard Gordh, George Gowan, Donald Grace, J. Peter Graham, George A. Grant, Robert Grant, J. Marse Gray, David B. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Gre-Gwi, Green, William B. Greenfield, Larry Gremillion, Joseph Gritson, Eric W. Groenfeldt, John S. Grimes, Jordan Grow, Lawrence Goodman, Howard Goodspeed, Stephen Gordon, Ernest Gornto, Talmage Goulet, Charles Gowan, Donald Grabner, Donald Grady, Albert Graf, Fred Graham, George Granskou, David Grant, Robert Greaves, Richard Green, William Grimm, Harold Grodzins, Morton Groskreutz, Donald Grow, Brimson Guder, Darrell Likens Guinn, Thomas Gunn, Janet Gunn, Giles Gustaw, Romuald Guth, Alan Gustafson, C.V. Gustafson, James M. Guthridge, Frank Gwinn, Robert (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Ha-Haz, Haas, Harold Hadsell, John S. Haekel, Josef Hager, Jean Hakes, Edward Haines, Harold Halfpenny, Harold Hall, Robert Handspicker, M.B. Halvorson, John V. Halvorson, Loren Hammond, Blaine Hamre, James S. Handy, Robert Hankey, William C. Hansen, Herbert Hanson, Carl A. Hanson, Hazel Hanson, Paul Handspicker, M.B. Harbison, Elmore Harris Harding, Harold Harding, Vincent Hardman, Virgil Harkins, George Hardy, Henry Orlanders Harms, Abraham John Harmon, Lindsey Harnwell, Gaylord P. Haroutunian, Joseph Harper, Stanley Harrelson, Walter Harris, Charles U. Harris, Jack Harris, T. George Harold, Harris Harris, Roger Harrison, Paul Harrison, R.W. Harshbarger, Luther Hart, George F. Hart, James Hartley, R. Hartman, Forrest Hartmann, Henry Havard University Harvey, Xen Haselden, Kyle Hatlestad, Selmer Haughey, Malcolm Hausner, Marion Havens, Paul S. Hawes, Harold Hawley, Deborah Haydon, Harold Hazelton, Roger (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hea-Hy, Heald, Henry Healy, George Heartberg, Joseph Heber, Margaret Heckethorne, Gene Heer, Daniel Hefner, Philip Heiges, Donald Heller, Friedrich Heiler, F. Heinecken, Martin Heles, Frederic Helms, Roy Heiserman, A.R. Helmsing, Charles Henry, Carl Henry, Edward A. Henry, Rosetta Henson, Tom D. Herhold, Robert Herman, Stewart Herman, Stewart Herman, D. Stewart Herrlin, Olof Hershaberger, G. Ben Heschel, Abraham Helsa, David H. Higi, William L.Hilgert, Earle Hill, Lucy Ann Hill, George W. Hiltner, Seward Hilton, Randall Hinde, Canisus Hinderlie, Carroll Hintz, M. Hirai, Naofusa Hjelm, Norman Hodges, Eva Hofmann, Hans Hoffman, Hester Hoffman, Paul E. Holland, Richard Holborn, Hajo Holbrook, Clyde- Holdon, John Holleroth, Hugo Hollan, Ellis Holm, Carl Holman, Charles Holman, Charles Homans, Peter Hong, Theodore Holtzmann, David Marshall Hood, Rodney Hopkins, Paul Hopwood, G.R. Hordern, William Hori, Ichiro Horn, Henry Horton, Gertrude Hoskins, Fred Hoss, Loren Hotchkin, John F. Housewright, George Howe, Reuel Howell, James Hoyt, Robert Hudson, Winthrop Hulme, William Hungerford, O.D. Hunter, Barton Huntley, John F. Hushaw, Charles Hushaw, Charles C. Hutchins, Robert Maynard Hyde Park Printers (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Ida-Juv, Ida, Mary Ann Idinopulos, Thomas Ikenberry, Ann Ikenberry, Oliver Illingworth, Alfred Interchurch News Interseminary Faculties Union Israel, Consulate General of Jackson, Herbert Jackson, Renwick Jacobs, Melvan James, Alix Jamison, Leland Jarman, W. J. Jarvinen, Veikko Jay, Eric Jellema, William Jenkins, Daniel Jennings, Louis Jensen, Ad. Jensen, Erling Jenson, Robert Jeremias, Joachim Johannessen, G.G. John, Peter H. Johnson, D. Gale Johnson, Edward Johnson, Gerald K. Johnson, Howard Johnson, R. Francis Johnson, Richard N. Johnson, Richard Norris Johnson, R. Francis Johnson, R. Lewis Johnson, Ralph M. Johnson, William A. Johnston, Frank E. Jones, Harry W. Jones, Lewis Webster Jones, Robert G. Jordahl, Roger Steen Josselyn, Franklyn Joyce, Robert E. Judy, Marvin Jurji, Edward Juva, Mikko (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Kallas, James Kanter, Milton Kantzenbach, F.W. Katagiri, Mineo Katz, Wilber Kaufman, Gordon Kaufmann, John Keeling, J. Keith Kegley, Charles Keir, Harold Keisler, E.B. Keister, J. D. Keith, William Kelley, Dean Kelly, Frances Kendall, John Kennedy, Gerald Kennedy, Winston Keppler, Paul Kent, Jack Kern, Richard Kerner, Otto Kerney, LeRoy Kerridge, Jack Kesich, Veselin Ketchum, Robert Key, Andrew Keyser, W.H. Kilgallen, John Kiley, Roger Killinger, John Kimpton, Lawrence Kindem, Ingolf King, Martin Luther, Jr. King, Sam King, Winston Kinsey, H.D. Kirschenmann, Fred (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Kit-Kup, Kitagawa, Joseph Kiwiet, John Kjeseth, Peter Klausli, Richard Klett, Guy Klever, Gerald Klick, Cora Kloetzli, Walter Kmet, William Knaus, Earl Kneebone, Leon Knight, Jerry Knopf, Edwin Knowles, Richard Knudsen, Johannes Knutson, David Knutson, Kent Koch, Hal Koehler, John Koenker, Ernest Kogan, Herman Von Kompenhausen, Kopplin, David Kort, Wesley Kozak, Joe Kraeling, Carl Kraft, Virgil Kramer, Stephanie Krauss, Paul Kreider, Eugene Kreider, Lorrin Krebs, Sandra Kretzmann, A. R. Kring, Walter Krodel, Gottfried Krogman, Weston Ksemori, Patricia Kucheman, Clark Kuhnle, Harold Kuhns, Frederick Kula, T.A. Kuniholm, Roland Kunst, D. Hermann Kupcinet, Irv (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - L-Leu, Laeuchli, Sam LaFleur, Alfred Laing, Chester Lambert, Rollins Lamotte, Etienne Lang, Reuben Landmann, Paul Landry, Hedy Lane, William Larsen, Edward Larson, Arthur Larson, W. Douglas Larsson, Edvin Larsen, Edward Latourette, Kenneth Scott Lautenslager, E. S. Law, Williard Lawrence, Richard Lazareth, William Lea, William Leavenworth, Lynn Le Couteur, E. R. Ledbetter, J. T. Ledger, Thomas Lee, Conrad Lee, Richard William Lee, Robert E.A. Leen, Walter V. Lefevre, Hanns Lefevre, Perry Lehmann, Helmut Leibrecht, Walter Leiser, John Leland, Simeon Lentz, Harold Lentz, Thomas Lerner, Michael LeSaint, William Lessly, Stiles Lester, Donald Lester, Julius Letts, Harold Leuschli, Samuel (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Levi, Edward Levi, Julian (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Lewellyn Studio Lewis, Ronald Lewis, Thomas Lightfoot, William Lightner, Quentin Lilje, Hanns Lincicome, Arthur Lindgren, Elvin Lindquist, Emory Lindsell, Harold Lish, Gordon Little, Lester Lloyd, Glen Loder, Dwight Loetscher, Lefferts Loew, Cornelius Loew, Ralph Loftus, Joseph Logan, Howard Logan, Leila Lohmann, Christoph Lokken, Sigurd Long, Charles Loomer, Bernard The Lookout Lord, John Wesley Lotz, Nick Louzecky, David Love, Thomas Luce, Henry Luecke, Richard Lueders, Albert Luke, Cornelius Luman, Richard Lunding, Franklin Lundeen, Malvin Lusby, F. Stanley Lutheran Assembly Office Lutheran Companion Lutheran Messenger Lutnes, Robert Luyster, Robert Lynn, Robert (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - McBride, Katharine McCarn, Ruth McClear, James McCleave, Paul McConnell, Enid McCord, James McCorkle, Henry McCormack, Arthur McCormack, Clyde McCormick Theological Seminary McCue, James McCurry, Allan McCutcheon, W.J. McDermott, F.W. McDill, Thomas McDonough, John McDonough, Thomas McElroy, David McElwain, Hugh McGiffert, Cushman McGrath, Brendan MacGregor, Geddes McKay, Orville McKay, Arthur McKenzie, John McLean, Milton McLean, Stuart (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - McM-Mead, McManus, William McNeill, John T. McNeill, William H. McShane, Carl Macalester College MacAllister, Miriam MacCorquodale, D. W. MacBryde, Duncan MacGregor, Geddes Mack, Walter Mackin, Benjamin MacLear, James MacLennan, David MacLeod, Donald Madsen, David Magnuson, J. Otto Maguire, James Main, W.R. Maitland, David Makarewicz, Sylvester Malone, Edward Mandic, Vukusava Manschreck, Clyde Marcel, Gabriel Marks, Rachel Maroon, Chicago Marple, Dorothy Marshall, Robert Martin, James Marty, Martin Marvin, John Marziniak, Edward Mason, Dorothy Masterson, Reginald Mather, P. Boyd Matthew, Harold Matthews, William Matthias, Ronald Mattson, Karl Maura, Sister Maxant, William Maxfield, Donald David May, Harry Maye, Arthur Mayer, Herbert Meacham, Paul Mead, Leonard Mead, Sidney (Box 9, Folder 4)